Contact

jasir.tp13@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jasirtp-0673a493 (LinkedIn) jasirtp.github.io/jasu/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Arduino Web Development css

JASIR TP

Full stack developer

Malappuram

Summary

Experienced Web Development with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in SQL, C++, C (Programming Language), HTML, and Software Development. Strong business development professional with a Master of Science - MS focused in Computer Science from SS College Areekode.

Experience

Talrop

Software Engineer December 2020 - Present (4 months)

Kochi, Kerala, India

Pibots

IoT Consultant

June 2019 - December 2020 (1 year 7 months)

Calicut Area, India

Kerala Startup Mission

Chief Executive Officer

June 2018 - December 2020 (2 years 7 months)

Areekode

Chief Executive Officer SS iedc

Sylcon Shoes & Bags
Information Technology Assistant

June 2017 - May 2018 (1 year)

Ernakulam, Kerala, India

Stock auditor & IT assistant

kickc innovations

Developer

January 2015 - June 2017 (2 years 6 months)

Education

University of Calicut

Master of Science - MS, Computer Science · (2018 - 2020)

Calicut University, Thenhipalem, Malapuram BCA, Computer Science · (2014 - 2017)